itsalltech.com 2012-06-21

# Privacy Policy | It's All Tech

The following is the most up-to-date privacy policy for It's All Tech. You are expected to read this policy prior to using any of It's All Tech's services.

If you have any questions that were not addressed in this privacy policy, feel free to contact It's All Tech.

It's All Tech takes the privacy of its readers extremely seriously. It's All Tech will never, under any circumstance, sell your information, including username, password, email address, and IP address, to any third-party companies and/or entities. This privacy policy was compiled so that you, the reader, have a good understanding of the information collected every time you visit It's All Tech, as well as what It's All Tech will do in the rare event of a security breach.

### 1\. What does this privacy policy apply to?

This privacy policy applies to all portions of It's All Tech and its subdomains, excluding the Livefyre commenting system used on It's All Tech. This policy does not apply to any other websites on the Internet, nor does it apply to websites that are currently or will be linked on It's All Tech. This circumstance includes advertisements found on It's All Tech. It's All Tech is not responsible for other websites privacy policies, nor what information those websites may collect.

### 2\. What data does It's All Tech collect from its readers?

Every time you, the reader, visit It's All Tech, the following information is collected and stored for further viewing in the It's All Tech database and analytics software: IP address, Internet Service Provider (ISP), Web browser, Web browser version, Operating System (OS), Flash version, Screen resolution, JavaScript information, the time it took to load each individual page, your location (down to the city), the time you spent on It's All Tech, your username and password (if logged in), and search queries conducted. In addition, cookies are gathered by our third-party advertisements providers (Google) to display relevant advertisements on It's All Tech.

It's All Tech will never give this information away to third-party companies, nor will it be sold to other entities outside of It's All Tech. The information gathered is used solely for statistical and security purposes.

### 3\. What happens if I, the reader, am being spammed by another user on It's All Tech?

The best course of action that you, the reader, should take in the event that you are receiving spam is to contact an It's All Tech administrator immediately. Administrators will then investigate the situation and if deemed necessary, the user who spammed will be banned from viewing all parts of It's All Tech. Re-registration or hacking to continue to use It's All Tech after a ban will result in a more serious consequence.

### 4\. Children under 13

It's All Tech prohibits children under the age of 13 to register for an account on It's All Tech. It's All Tech will never, knowingly, allow a child under the age of 13 to register for an account. In the event that It's All Tech is sent personal information from a child under the age of 13, the information is deleted as quickly as possible. Please do not send It's All Tech information or data if you are under the age of 13. In addition, It's All Tech does not collect statistical information, as described above, from children under the age of 13.

### 5\. Use of any/all information gathered by It's All Tech from readers

If information is gathered automatically, such as your IP address or Web browser, It's All Tech will use this data only for statistics and security purposes. In the case It's All Tech is sent information, such as a news "tip" or article idea, that information may or may not be used publicly on It's All Tech.

### 6\. Disabling your It's All Tech account and clearing all cookies related to It's All Tech

In the event that you would like to close your It's All Tech account, please email brian [at] itsalltech [dot] com with your username and password. Your account will be closed and all information regarding it will be permanently removed from our database within 48 hours of your initial request. This decision is not reversible.

### 7\. Forgetting your It's All Tech username and/or password

In the event you, the reader, forget your username to It's All Tech, It's All Tech staff is not obligated to assist you to retrieve the username. The main purpose for this policy is because of security concerns.

In the event that you, the reader, forget the password to your It's All Tech account, simply use the utility found in the following webpage to recover it: <http://itsalltech.com/wp-login.php?action=lostpassword>.

### 8\. Visitors outside the United States of America

Please keep in mind that It's All Tech is operated inside the United States of America. In the event that you, the reader, send It's All Tech information, data, or something else, it is subject to United States law, copyright, and data protection. If you, the reader, submit something to It's All Tech that is against United States law, It's All Tech staff is obligated to report you to law enforcement.

### 9\. Confidentiality

It's All Tech reserves the right to deny you, the reader, access to staff member information and other user information. Unless It's All Tech receives written permission from the other person you are requesting information from, It's All Tech may not share any information with you.

### 10\. Tampering and/or modifying any parts of the It's All Tech website

Tampering and/or modifying any parts of the It's All Tech website, including inserting malicious code and/or hacking, is prohibited and will involve consequences. The customization features that It's All Tech provides by default are allowed to be used. 

### 11\. Purchases through the It's All Tech gear store

Purchases made through the It's All Tech official gear store (hosted by Printfection) are made securely. Your credit card information, nor your physical address, will never be shared to It's All Tech staff. Should there be a security breach at Printfection, Printfection holds all responsibility for contacting you - not It's All Tech. It's All Tech is not responsible for any credit card information being stolen as part of the purchasing process. Should you, the reader, not be happy with your purchase made at the official It's All Tech gear store, simply send the product back to Printfection for a refund. Never use any other gear store to purchase It's All Tech gear (only <http://printfection.com/itsalltech>)

### 12\. Changes to the privacy policy

This privacy policy may be modified at any point in time. It's All Tech is not obligated to inform you when this privacy policy changes. The latest version of the privacy policy for It's All Tech is always available here: <http://itsalltech.com/privacy>.

The following information of this privacy policy discusses the plan of action following a security breach at It's All Tech where user information may or may not have been taken.

In the rare event of a security breach at It's All Tech, our servers will immediately be shut down to prevent further attacks. Our web host will immediately be notified in the case that there was a security breach. Immediately following these two actions, a site-wide email will be sent out to all users and staff members explaining the details of the breach (if available at that time).

Following the email being sent out, the staff of It's All Tech will work to find the source of the attack and make sure that no further attacks will occur. If deemed necessary, law enforcement will be notified shortly after the security breach occurred.

A minimum five-hour downtime will occur in the event of a security breach at It's All Tech, whether user information was taken or not.
